How long has it been since your last confession?
Bad Sister is a thriller, tv movie film directed by Doug Campbell.
As a top student at St.
Adeline's Catholic Boarding School, Zoe senses that something is not quite right about the school's new nun-- a sense
proven to be true when it is revealed the "good' nun is an imposter with a fatal attraction to Zoe's brother.
Laura, played by Alyshia Ochse.
Jason, played by Devon Werkheiser.
Zoe, played by Ryan Whitney.
Sister Rebecca, played by Helen Eigenberg.
David, played by Robert Leeshock.
Cheryl, played by Lise Simms.
Bad Sister is a 1931 American pre-Code drama film directed by Hobart Henley.
The screenplay by Edwin H.
Knopf, Tom Reed, and Raymond L.
Schrock is based on the 1913 novel The Flirt by Booth
Tarkington, which had been filmed in 1916 and 1922.
The film marks the screen debuts of both Bette Davis and
Sidney Fox (who was billed over Davis).
The cast also includes Humphrey Bogart and ZaSu Pitts in supporting roles.
Bad Sister has been preserved in the Library of Congress collection.
The tone is intense.